Weepholes	排水孔
Reinstatement Works	修復工程
antiquated	陳舊的
sentiment	情绪
Cofferdam	围堰
Cavern	洞穴
CARBON DIOXIDE IS a problem. And everyone knows the best thing to do with problems is bury them deep in the ground and forget they ever existed.

basalt	玄武岩
have long touted	长期吹捧
wean	断奶
SYNOPSIS 簡介
esoteric	深奥的
arcane	神秘
vignettes	 小插圖
tavern	酒馆
conspirator	阴谋家
You will be judged by what you do, not what you say.

singularity	奇異，獨一
salvage		打捞， 回收利用
professes	自稱
emerge		浮现，出现
happy with sb./sth	对某人某事表示满意
diversify into	进入某个领域，朝某个方向发展
be faced with	面对某种局面
stay loyal to	对…保持忠诚
be committed to	对…作出承诺
recession	衰退期
notable		格外地，特别的
deficit		逆差、亏损、赤字
remained	依然，继续，留下
infrastructure	基础设施（如运输、通讯、银行制度等）；基础结构
Plinth		基座
Spoil		廢品
exasperating	使人恼怒的
contend		斗争
UUV		unmanned undersea vehicle
umbilical
emancipate
venomous	有毒的
nefarious		邪恶的
venom		毒液
chock		满满地
insecticides	杀虫剂
fuss		忙乱
vat		大桶
slate		石板

A-送行人员 B-客户 C-送行人员
A: Now, it's 8:30. We arrived just on time.
B: Ok. I think I have to buy the departure tax.
A: Let me do it for you.
B: Thank you very much. Mr. Liu, I have to say goodbye now. But before that, I'd like to say it has been a very pleasant and productive trip for me. Your company has left me a very good impression, and I am deeply moved by your hospitality. I think our cooperation will be a very successful one.
C: Thank you very much, Mr. Washington. You are playing a very important part in the cooperation. We hope we can hear from you soon.
A: Here is the receipt of the airport fee.
B: Miss. Li, my dear friend. Thank you very much for all your help. You are really very helpful and thoughtful. I believe Mr. Liu is very lucky to have your assistance.
A: Thank you. It's very kind of you to say so. I'm really happy for having worked with you for a few days. I really hope to see you again some day and we are looking forward to hearing from you.
B: Thank you again. Bye-bye.
C: We wish you a safe and pleasant journey home.
A: Have a nice journey.
B: Thank you. Bye-bye.
